[
  {
    "Question :": "Which testing is done by developer?",
    "A :": "Unit Testing",
    "Answer :": "A",
    "B :": "Integration Testing",
    "C :": "Sanity Testing",
    "D :": "Regression Testing"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Which is functional testing?",
    "A :": "Load Testing",
    "Answer :": "C",
    "B :": "Security Testing",
    "C :": "Gorilla Testing",
    "D :": "Benchmark Testing"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Quality Assuarance is a _______ Process.",
    "A :": "Validation",
    "Answer :": "D",
    "B :": "Specification",
    "C :": "Testing",
    "D :": "Verification"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Quality Control is a _______ Process.",
    "A :": "Validation",
    "Answer :": "A",
    "B :": "Specification",
    "C :": "Testing",
    "D :": "Verification"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Which statement is correct?",
    "A :": "Validation occurs after Verification",
    "Answer :": "A",
    "B :": "Verification occurs after Validation",
    "C :": "Validation and Verification occurs together",
    "D :": "None of them"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Verification is a part of ?",
    "A :": "Validation ",
    "Answer :": "C",
    "B :": "Software Testing",
    "C :": "Quality Assurance",
    "D :": "Unit Testing"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Validation is a part of ?",
    "A :": "Validation ",
    "Answer :": "B",
    "B :": "Software Testing",
    "C :": "Quality Assurance",
    "D :": "Unit Testing"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Which can be done by automation?",
    "A :": "Validation ",
    "Answer :": "A",
    "B :": "Software Testing",
    "C :": "Quality Assurance",
    "D :": "Verification"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Tests performed after development are called?",
    "A :": "Static Testing ",
    "Answer :": "C",
    "B :": "Software Testing",
    "C :": "Dynamic Testing",
    "D :": "None of them"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Defects which are accepted by developers are called?",
    "A :": "Error",
    "Answer :": "B",
    "B :": "Bug",
    "C :": "Fault",
    "D :": "None of them"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "How many testing types are there?",
    "A :": "1",
    "Answer :": "B",
    "B :": "2",
    "C :": "3",
    "D :": "4"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "How many testing methods are there?",
    "A :": "1",
    "Answer :": "C",
    "B :": "2",
    "C :": "3",
    "D :": "4"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Which is the highest level of testing?",
    "A :": "Black Box Testing",
    "Answer :": "C",
    "B :": "Grey Box Testing",
    "C :": "White Box Testing",
    "D :": "None of them"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "When we test only the major classes\/ functions in a test is called?",
    "A :": "Feature Testing",
    "Answer :": "D",
    "B :": "Regression Testing",
    "C :": "Unit Testing",
    "D :": "Smoke Testing"
  },
  {
    "Question :": "Which is the biggest testing of all?",
    "A :": "Feature Testing",
    "Answer :": "B",
    "B :": "Regression Testing",
    "C :": "Unit Testing",
    "D :": "Smoke Testing"
  }
]